(Amy:)We're also coming to you
live from a different apartment.
(Sheldon:)Dr. Fowler and I began an
experiment in living together
(Sheldon:)after her apartment
became water damaged.
(Sheldon:)This is our
friend Penny's place.
(Sheldon:)You may remember her
from our episode
(Sheldon:)And the People
Who Don't Understand Them."
(Amy:)So, in the spirit
of cohabitation,
(Amy:)the theme of today's episode
is flags of two regions
(Amy:)coming together as one.
(Amy:)Such as the flag of
St. Kitts and Nevis.
(Sheldon:)So, let's roll up our
"sleevis" and get to know Nevis.
Well, I-I like that, but
next time check with me.
(Amy:)Did you know that the flag
(Amy:)was designed by a student
named Edrice Lewis...
(Penny:)I can't believe I'm saying this,
but can we watch the news
(Penny:)or something?
(Leonard:)It's cute, they're having
fun living together.
(Penny:)Yeah, I wonder what
they're gonna do
(Penny:)when her apartment's ready.
(Bernadette:)Actually, it's been
ready for weeks.
(Leonard:)What do you mean?
(Bernadette:)Well, they finished
the work early,
(Bernadette:)but she's been telling Sheldon
they're behind schedule.
(Leonard:)So, she's just
been lying to him?
(Penny:)Well, you've lied to Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Yeah, but to make him leave,
(Leonard:)not to make him stay.
(Sheldon:)Buda and Pest
united to form Budapest.
(Sheldon:)And that's why Budapest
"Budabest."
(Sheldon:)Now.
(Howard:)Oh, right.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪